Alrighty. An 8.2-magnitude
earthquake devastates Pasadena...
(Sheldon:)...reducing mighty edifices to dust,
enguIfing the city in flames...
(Sheldon:)...the streets flow with blood
and echo with the cries of the wounded.
(Sheldon:)Oh, excellent choice.
Now, put on your hard hat and safety vest.
(Leonard:)Oh, fun. I get to spend
another night in front of our apartment...
(Leonard:)...dressed like one of the Village People.
(Sheldon:)You make that joke every three months,
I still don't get it. Leonard, wait.
(Sheldon:)- What are you doing?
- I don't know. What am I doing?
(Sheldon:)Look around you, there's hypothetical
broken glass everywhere.
(Sheldon:)Really? You're going to face Armageddon
without your orthotics? Your choice.
- Uh-oh! Hypothetical aftershock.
- Unh! Aah!
(Sheldon:)And that's why we wear hard hats.